Eli, hey, Tony Kinkela with New England.
How you doing, man?
How you doing? Good, coach. Great.
Great. I'm going to pass you over to
Elliot Wolf right here. All right.
Eli, what's up, man?
How you doing, Mr. Wolf? You doing all
right?
Yes, sir. Doing good. All right, man.
The wait is over.
We're going to take you here.
And congratulations. We're excited about
it. You with family right now?
Yep. Yep. Hanging out with family. Are
you going to be there?
Yeah, in Iowa. Awesome. [music]
Well, congratulations, man. We just sent
it in. Here's coach Vrabel.
Thank you so much.
Eli.
What's up, coach? Hey, man. Congrats.
You ready to get to work?
>> Thank you. I'm ready. I'm ready. Thank
you so much.
>> [music]
>> I know, buddy. We we're excited to have
you.
Just come in here ready to work and and
compete [music] and improve and and like
I said, we're excited.
Everybody here is looking forward to
getting to work with you and
you know, it's going [music] to be a
it's going to be a great journey for
you.
Yeah, can't wait to get to work, coach.
Thank you so much. Okay, man. See you.
Bye. [music]
Job, boys. Got another feeling.
>> [applause]